Ask him yourself.
اسأله بنفسك.
if he agreed
إذا وافق
to catch the flower thief with me?
للقبض على لص الزهرة معي؟
Father-in-law, I did agree.
والد الزوج ، أنا موافق.
This has something to do with Ziyu.
هذا له علاقة بـ Ziyu.
I should kneel.
علي الركوع.
Ziyu.
zyu.
You don't have to defend her.
ليس عليك الدفاع عنها.
I just can't bear to
أنا فقط لا أستطيع أن أتحمل
I couldn't bear to extinguish her passion.
لم أستطع تحمل إطفاء شغفها.
That's why I went with her.
لهذا السبب ذهبت معها.
In addition, I'm afraid there might be a loophole.
بالإضافة إلى ذلك ، أخشى أنه قد تكون هناك ثغرة.
Xin Huan, is Zi Yu right?
شين هوان ، هل زي يو على حق؟
Yes. It's just...
نعم.  انه فقط...
Just what?
فقط ماذا؟
Let me tell you.
دعني أخبرك.
Don't do whatever you want
لا تفعل ما تريد
just because Zi Yu favors you.
فقط لأن Zi Yu تفضلك.
I'm not dead yet.
أنا لم يمت بعد.
Tonight...
الليلة...
You're not allowed to eat tonight as punishment.
لا يُسمح لك بتناول الطعام الليلة كعقاب.
Father.
أب.
Mother.
الأم.
Madam, stand up.
سيدتي ، قفي.
Don't be afraid.
لا تخافوا.
I
أنا
prepared chicken drumsticks for you.
أفخاذ الدجاج المعدة لك.
What kind of game is this?
أي نوع من اللعبة هو هذا؟
You can't let the progress go down.
لا يمكنك أن تدع التقدم ينخفض.
Isn't it just a divorce?
أليس هذا مجرد طلاق؟
I don't believe it.
لا أصدق ذلك.
Prince Yu.
الأمير يو.
Get up.
استيقظ.
What's the matter, Madam?
ما بك سيدتي؟
I'm hungry.
أنا جائع.
But it's midnight now.
لكنه منتصف الليل الآن.
The servants are already resting.
الخدم يستريحون بالفعل.
How about
ماذا عن
I heat up the drumsticks for you?
أنا سخن أفخاذ الطبل من أجلك؟
You even pissed me off with drumsticks.
حتى أنك أغضبتني بأعواد الطبل.
You...
أنت...
Go to the kitchen
اذهب الى المطبخ
Make me something to eat.
اجعلني شيئا لاكله
Okay.
تمام.
What would you like to eat?
ماذا تريد أن تأكل؟
It's late at night.
انها ساعة متأخرة من الليل.
Ramyeon?
راميون؟
Madam.
سيدتي.
Here.
هنا.
Ramyeon.
راميون.
What is it?
ما هذا؟
It's just
انه فقط
It's fine noodles.
إنها معكرونة جيدة.
Then roll it up
ثم نشمر
After frying it with oil
بعد قليها بالزيت
Just cook it in the pot
فقط اطبخه في القدر
Eating oil at midnight
تناول الزيت عند منتصف الليل
It's bad for your health.
إنه مضر بصحتك.
You don't know how to eat.
أنت لا تعرف كيف تأكل.
Otherwise, how can you complete the task?
وإلا كيف يمكنك إكمال المهمة؟
It's just for shape.
إنها فقط من أجل الشكل.
Actually you need to cook it
في الواقع أنت بحاجة لطهيها
And the instant noodles
والمعكرونة سريعة التحضير
can be stored for a long time
يمكن تخزينها لفترة طويلة
it can be stored for a long time.
يمكن تخزينها لفترة طويلة.
For example, after three or five months,
على سبيل المثال ، بعد ثلاثة أو خمسة أشهر ،
I want to eat.
أريد أن آكل.
It's still edible.
لا يزال صالحًا للأكل.
While you were away,
بينما كنت بعيدا
it rained heavily in the Star Kingdom.
أمطرت بغزارة في Star Kingdom.
and caused a flood.
وتسبب في فيضان.
The grains reserved by the people
الحبوب المحفوظة من قبل الناس
were flooded.
غمرت المياه.
The instant noodles you just mentioned
المكرونة سريعة التحضير التي ذكرتها للتو
can be stored for months?
يمكن تخزينها لأشهر؟
Of course.
بالتاكيد.
You don't have to do it.
ليس عليك القيام بذلك.
At worst,
في أسوأ الأحوال،
I'll just starve.
سوف أتضور جوعا.
Your Ladyship is kind.
سيدتك لطيفة.
I'll do it now.
سأفعل ذلك الآن.
You're taking advantage of me even if you make instant noodles.
أنت تستغلني حتى لو كنت تصنع المكرونة سريعة التحضير.
Madam.
سيدتي.
The noodles are ready.
المعكرونة جاهزة.
Prince Yu.
الأمير يو.
You really made it?
هل فعلتها حقا؟
Yes.
نعم.
Smells good.
تبدو رائحته طيبة.
I'm flattered.
أنا أشعر بالإطراء.
You taught me well.
لقد علمتني جيدا.
Try it.
جربها.
Okay.
تمام.
Ma'am.
أملك
Your hand...
يدك...
It's fine.
لا بأس.
I should feel sorry for you.
يجب أن أشعر بالأسف من أجلك.
Eat up.
أكل.
Eat.
تأكل.
Take your time.
خذ وقتك.
I made a lot of instant noodles.
لقد صنعت الكثير من المكرونة سريعة التحضير.
Later,
لاحقاً،
I can ask Zimu and Chuntao
يمكنني أن أسأل Zimu و Chuntao
to cook for you.
لطهي الطعام من أجلك.
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو.
You don't have to bow, Lord Gao.
ليس عليك أن تنحني يا لورد جاو.
Is there any way
هل هناك أي طريقة
can be solved?
يمكن حلها؟
Your Highness.
صاحب السمو.
The treasury of Tianxing is empty now.
خزانة تيانشينغ فارغة الآن.
and there is also a flood in the south.
وحدث فيضان ايضا في الجنوب.
If you can
إذا كنت تستطيع
solve the food problem,
حل مشكلة الغذاء ،
right?
الصحيح؟
Song Zi Private Bank
بنك سونغ زي الخاص
in a million taels of silver.
بمليون تايل من الفضة.
I’ll change them all into grains
سوف أقوم بتحويلهم جميعًا إلى حبوب
Can it be solved?
هل يمكن حلها؟
If you can solve the flood,
إذا كنت تستطيع حل الفيضان ،
His Majesty will set you free.
جلالة الملك سوف يحررك.
Then do it.
إذا إفعلها.
Yes.
نعم.
By the way, Lord Gao,
بالمناسبة ، اللورد جاو ،
Yu Xinhuan.
يو شينهوان.
You're back, right?
لقد عدت ، أليس كذلك؟
That's true.
هذا صحيح.
I see.
أرى.
This plaster
هذا الجص
is from our ancestors.
من أسلافنا.
Really.
هل حقا.
It's good for your skin.
إنه جيد لبشرتك.
and your skin will turn white.
وستتحول بشرتك إلى اللون الأبيض.
Skin?
بشرة؟
Of course.
بالتاكيد.
These are ancestral herbs.
هذه أعشاب أسلاف.
Smell it.
شمها.
Doesn't it smell good?
أليست رائحتها طيبة؟
Boss
رئيس
Excuse me.
اعذرني.
which one
أي واحد
Which one is it?
أي واحد هو؟
Heating cream.
كريم تسخين.
Thank you, boss.
شكرا لك يا رئيس.
Ms. Yu.
السيدة يو.
Why did you buy burn cream?
لماذا اشتريت كريم الحروق؟
Someone in the mansion got burned.
شخص ما في القصر احترق.
It's urgent.
انها عاجل.
The people in the mansion got burned.
احترق الناس في القصر.
Why are you buying it yourself?
لماذا تشتريها بنفسك؟
Did you burn yourself?
هل حرقت نفسك؟
Eunuch! Eunuch!
الخصي!  الخصي!
No way! It's not him!
مستحيل!  إنه ليس هو!
It's her. It's her who burned your father.
إنها هي.  هي التي أحرقت والدك.
No, no.
مجتهد.
It's not like that
إنه ليس كذلك